Finding aid for the Experiments in Art and Technology records, 1966-1993 (bulk 1966-1973)
Experiments in Art and Technology records
- Audio tapes, 1966-1993; Series VII.; ca. 8.5 lin. ft. 13 boxes
  - Sound cassettes, ca. 1967-1971
    - E.A.T. meetings, conferences, other projects (Cassette C78-C154D)
      - Anand Buffalo Project, Ahmedabad, India, 1969 Dec 12 (Cassette C110-C113a)
        - E.A.T. Meeting in India on Buffalo Project, Tape 2 (Cassette C111)
          Side A and B labels: EAT Meeting in India on Buffalo Project 12/12/1969 #2. Paper insert: "...Ref 111 tape 2."
          2 sound tape reels of 2 (65 min., 27 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
          1 sound disc (65 min., 27 sec.) (CD): digital. Copy master.
        - E.A.T. Meeting in India on Buffalo Project, Tape 3 (Cassette C112)
          1 sound cassette (64 min., 10 sec.): analog. Original.
          Side A and B labels: EAT Meeting in India on Buffalo Project 12/12/1969 #3. Paper insert: "...Ref 112 tape 3."
          2 sound tape reels of 2 (64 min., 10 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
          1 sound disc (64 min., 10 sec.) (CD): digital. Copy master.
        - E.A.T. Meeting in India on Buffalo Project, Tape 4 (Cassette C113)
          1 sound cassette (51 min., 07 sec.): analog. Original.
          Side A and B labels: EAT Meeting in India on Buffalo Project 12/12/1969 #4. Paper insert: "...Ref 113 tape 4."
          2 sound tape reels of 2 (51 min., 07 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
          1 sound disc (51 min., 07 sec.) (CD): digital. Copy master.
        - E.A.T. Meeting in India on Buffalo Project, Tape 5 (Cassette C113a)
          1 sound cassette (64 min., 21 sec.): analog. Original.
          Side A and B labels: EAT Meeting in India on Buffalo Project 12/12/1969 #5. Paper insert: "...Ref 113A tape 5."
          2 sound tape reels of 2 (64 min., 21 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
          1 sound disc (64 min., 21 sec.) (CD): digital. Copy master.
          1 sound disc (64 min., 21 sec.) (CD): digital. Use copy.
        - E.A.T. Meeting in India on Buffalo Project, Tape 6 (Cassette C113b)
          1 sound cassette (65 min., 20 sec.): analog. Original.
          Side A and B labels: EAT Meeting in India on Buffalo Project 12/12/1969 #6. Paper insert: "...Ref 113B Tape 6 tape is broken and come off reel and must be repaired before playing."
          2 sound tape reels of 2 (65 min., 20 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
          1 sound disc (65 min., 20 sec.) (CD): digital. Copy master.
        - E.A.T. Meeting in India on Buffalo Project, Tape 7 (Cassette C113c)
          1 sound cassette (61 min., 35 sec.): analog. Original.
          Side A and B labels: EAT Meeting in India on Buffalo Project 12/12/1969 #7. Paper insert: "...Ref 113C tape 7."
          2 sound tape reels of 2 (61 min., 35 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
          1 sound disc (61 min., 35 sec.) (CD): digital. Copy master.
        - E.A.T. Meeting in India on Buffalo Project, Tape 8 (Cassette C113d)
          1 sound cassette (61 min., 45 sec.): analog. Original.
          Side A and B labels: EAT Meeting in India on Buffalo Project 12/12/1969 #8. Paper insert: "...Ref 113D tape 8."
          2 sound tape reels of 2 (61 min., 45 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
          1 sound disc (61 min., 45 sec.) (CD): digital. Copy master.
      - American Artists in India: interviews, undated, 1969? (Cassette C114-C122)
        - Steve Paxton interview, 1 of 2 (Cassette C114)
          1 sound cassette (60 min., 32 sec.): analog. Original.
          Side 1: Steve Paxton interview 1 of 2. Side 2: Steve Paxton cont'd. Paper insert: "EAT Steve Paxton Interview on American Artists in India Ref # 114 1 of 2."
          2 sound tape reels of 2 (60 min., 32 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
          1 sound disc (60 min., 32 sec.) (CD): digital. Copy master.
        - Steve Paxton interview, 2 of 2 (Cassette C115)
          1 sound cassette (59 min., 45 sec.): analog. Original.
          Side 1: Steve Paxton interview 2 of 2. Side 2: Steve Tape II. Paper insert: "Steve Paxton Interview on American Artists in India Ref # 115 2 of 2."
          2 sound tape reels of 2 (59 min., 45 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
          1 sound disc (59 min., 45 sec.) (CD): digital. Copy master.
        - Trisha Brown interview, 1 of 2 (Cassette C116)
          1 sound cassette (31 min., 24 sec.): analog. Original.
          Side A: EAT Trisha Brown interview 1 of 2. Side B: Trisha #2. Paper insert: "EAT Trisha Brown interview on American Artists in Inda Ref 116 1 of 2."
          2 sound tape reels of 2 (31 min., 24 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
          1 sound disc (31 min., 24 sec.) (CD): digital. Copy master.
        - Trisha Brown interview, 2 of 2 (Cassette C117)
          1 sound cassette (19 min., 36 sec.): analog. Original.
          Side A: EAT Trisha Brown interview 2 of 2. Side B: Trisha #4. Paper insert: "EAT Trisha Brown interview on American Artists in Inda Ref 117 2 of 2."
          2 sound tape reels of 2 (19 min., 36 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
          1 sound disc (19 min., 36 sec.) (CD): digital. Copy master.
        - LaMonte Young, Marian Zazeela interview, 1 of 3 (Cassette C118)
          1 sound cassette (30 min., 29 sec.): analog. Original.
          Side 1: EAT: Lamonte Young / Marian Zazeela interview 1 of 3. Side 2: LaMonte & Marian. Paper insert: "LaMonte Young / Marian Zazeela Int. American Artists in India Ref #118 1 of 3."
          2 sound tape reels of 2 (30 min., 29 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
          1 sound disc (30 min., 29 sec.) (CD): digital. Copy master.
        - LaMonte Young, Marian Zazeela interview, 2 of 3 (Cassette C119)
          1 sound cassette (30 min., 35 sec.): analog. Original.
          Side 1: EAT: Lamonte Young / Marian Zazeela interview 2 of 3. Side 2: L-M. Paper insert: "LaMonte Young / Marian Zazeela Int. American Artists in India Ref #119 2 of 3."
          2 sound tape reels of 2 (30 min., 35 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
          1 sound disc (30 min., 35 sec.) (CD): digital. Copy master.
        - LaMonte Young, Marian Zazeela interview, 3 of 3; Jed Bark interview (Cassette C120)
          1 sound cassette (23 min., 25 sec.): analog. Original.
          Side A: EAT Lamonte Young / Marian Zazeela interview 3 of 3. Side B: EAT Jed Bark Interview. Paper insert: "EAT A: LaMonte Young/Marian Zazeela int. American Artists in India Ref #120 3 of 3" and "EAT B: Jed Bark interview on American Artists in India Ref #120 1 of 1."
          2 sound tape reels of 2 (23 min., 25 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
          1 sound disc (23 min., 25 sec.) (CD): digital. Copy master.
        - Bombay street sounds (Cassette C121)
          1 sound cassette (30 min., 50 sec.): analog. Original.
          Side A and B labels: EAT / BK Bombay Street Sounds. Paper insert: "EAT / BK B: Bombay Street Sounds recorded near Taj Mahal Hotel Ref #121."
          2 sound tape reels of 2 (30 min., 50 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
          1 sound disc (30 min., 50 sec.) (CD): digital. Copy master.
        - Steve Paxton interview, pt. 1 and 2 (Cassette C122a)
          2 sound cassettes of 2: analog. Originals. Both numbered 122A. Same as C114, C115. Not reformatted.
      - Billy Klüver recordings of meetings and material in Guatemala, Jul-Aug 1972 (Cassette C123-C128)
        - Recordings of meetings and material in Guatemala (Cassette C123)
          1 sound cassette (78 min., 21 sec.): analog. Original.
          Side A: EAT/BK Recording if [sic] meetings in Guatemala, 1972, 1 of 6. Side B: July 23 Side 2?. Paper insert: "EAT / BK Klüver recording of meetings and material in Guatemala, project to use television to teach farming techniques to peasants 7 & 8/1972 Ref #123 1 of 6."
          3 sound tape reels of 3 (78 min., 21 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
          2 sound discs of 2 (78 min., 21 sec.) (CDs): digital. Copy master.
        - Recordings of meetings and material in Guatemala (Cassette C124)
          1 sound cassette (42 min., 18 sec.): analog. Original.
          Side A: EAT / BK Recording if [sic] meetings in Guatemala, 1972 2 of 6. Side B: Side 2 [blank]. Paper insert: "EAT / BK Klüver recording of meetings and material in Guatemala, project to use television to teach farming techniques to peasants 7 & 8/1972 Ref #124 2 of 6."
          2 sound tape reels of 2 (42 min., 18 sec.): analog; 7 1/2 ips. Archival master.
          1 sound disc (CD) (42 min., 18 sec.): digital. Copy master.
        - Klüver recording of material in Guatemala, during project, undated (Cassette C124a-C128)
          5 cassettes of 5.
      - Children and Communication: background, discussions, undated (Cassette C129-131)
        3 cassettes of 3.
      - Island Eye Island Ear, Saranasc Lake, 1978 (Cassette C132-C136)
        - Tudor and Nakaya interview, undated (Cassette C132)
          1 sound cassette.
        - Tudor and Nakaya interview; O'Connell reporting on Saranac situation, 1978 Nov 24 (Cassette C133)
        - Fred Waldhauer /telephone call from Saranasc Lake, 1978 Nov 22 (Cassette C134)
        - Talking with Kudish on the island, 1978 Oct 12 (Cassette C135)
        - Island Eye Island E: Mapping the island with Hardy, 1978 Oct 29 (Cassette C136)
      - Stefan Olson interview with Klüver for Swedish radio, parts 1 and 2, 1978 Jun 4 (Cassette C137)
        1 sound cassette. [See also C138]
      - Side A: Jankowski CBS, talk; Olson interview with Klüver, part 3, 1982 Jun 4 1978 June 4 (Cassette C138)
        1 sound cassette. Side A: Jankowski, talk on technology and telecommunications. Side B: Olson interview with Klüver for Swedish radio, part 3 [See also C137]
      - James Rosenquist making the poster for the Xenon Benefit at Tandem Press, 8th Ave. NY, 1979 Feb (Cassette C139)
      - Tudor concert at Xenon, 1979 (Cassette C140-C141)
        2 sound cassettes.
      - Interview with Frank Dymnicki of Tandem Press about printing Jim Rosenquist's poster and the Xenon Benefit, undated (Cassette C142)
      - E.A.T. History - Interview with Fred Waldhauer on his biography and his involvement with artists and E.A.T., 1991 August 4 (Cassette C143A-C143B)
      - Billy Kluver dictating paper on E.A.T., Side A, undated (Cassette C144A)
        Title from label; Broken tape is off reel. Ref no. 144A. Reel 4a.
      - Billy Kluver dictating paper on E.A.T., Side A; Nine Evenings, Side B, 1993 Jun 6 undated (Cassette C144B)
        Paper insert: Billy Kluver dictating papers on E.A.T. Rainforest. Ref no. 144B. Tapes 5.
      - Öyvind Fahlström's Collage of Sounds, Side A and Side B (Cassette C145a)
        Paper insert: E.A.T. Art Öyvind Fahlström Collage tape with Swedith, English material from films, radio, plays, etc. Ref no. 145.
      - Öyvind Fahlström Collage Radio, Side A (Cassette C145b)
        Paper insert: ART Öyvind Fahlström Collage Radio. No. 145 1/1.
      - Klüver lecture, Toronto, 1968 (Cassette C147-C149)
        2 sound cassettes. [Not reformatted; See R147-R149]
        C147-194, 1 of 2, Side A: Paper insert: BK Kluver Torono lecture 1968 REf no. 147 1/2.
        C147-149, 2 of 2, Side A: Paper insert: BK Kluver Toronto Lecture 1968 Red no. 147-149 2/2. Second part of talk using vugraph, talking about mylar mirrors, chorus line and spherical mirrors.
      - Klüver talk at color convention (Cassette C150)
        1 sound cassette. [Not reformatted; See R150]
      - Annual meeting of AAAS, 1976 Feb 22 (Cassette C151-C154)
        4 sound cassettes of 4.
        Boston Environment of the Future - Klüver talk and Panel. Klüver talk "Conditions for Artists' Participation in Shaping the Environment."
      - Klüver and Andrew Ogielski conversation on preserving history; meeting on Tudor piece "Ocean,", 1993 (Cassette C154A-D)
        - EAT Billy Klüver and Andrew Ogielski conversation on preserving history, 1 of 2, 1993 Oct 23 (Cassette C154A)
        - EAT Billy Klüver and Andrew Ogielski conversation on preserving history, 2 of 2, 1993 Oct 30 (Cassette C154B)
        - EAT Billy Klüver, Andrew Ogielski, Sophia Ogielska and David Tudor meeting on Tudor piece "Ocean," 1 of 2, 1993 Dec 12 (Cassette 154C)
        - EAT Billy Klüver, Andrew Ogielski, Sophia Ogielska and David Tudor meeting on Tudor piece "Ocean," 2 of 2, 1993 Dec 12 (Cassette C154D)
    - Unnumbered cassettes
      - Island Eye Island Ear, undated (Cassette CU01-CU09)
        9 sound cassettes of 9.
      - Meeting [?], 1978 Oct 10 (Cassette CU10)
- Films and videos, 1974-1997; Series VIII.; 4 box(es)
  Contains seven videos and two 16 mm. films of various E.A.T. activities, and 64 super 8 films made while location scouting for "Island Eye Island Ear."
  - Films (16 mm.) and VHS cassettes (3/4"), ca. 1990-ca. 1997 (Box 233)
    - Mary Wigman, dancer; 9 Evenings; and Rauschenberg 65. (Cassette V1 A & B)
      2 videocassettes of 2.
      2 videos transferred (from film?) Oct 8, 1992 by Middlemarch Films. VHS and Betacam SP copies made Feb 24, 1998. Numbered 24 by E.A.T.
    - Some More Beginnings (Cassette V2, V3)
      2 videocassettes (9 min., 31 sec. each). V3 is a duplicate of V2.
      (video transferred by WNET) Numbered 25 by E.A.T.
    - The Great Big Mirror Project (Cassette V4)
      1 videocassette. (Video transferred by WNET.) Numbered 26 by E.A.T.
    - Peter Kowalski sculpture (Reel F1)
      1 film reel; 16 mm. [unnumbered, numbered by repository]. Reformatted use copy available.
      Documentary.
    - A Promise of Space... fulfilled. Fairchild Industries, made by Thirtyfive-sixteen, released by Image, 1975 (Reel F2)
      1 film reel (14 min.); col. 16 mm. [unnumbered, numbered by repository]
      Published educational film. Do not reformat. About future space technology.
    - 9 evenings: theatre and engineering trailer, 1997 (Cassette V5)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (5 min., 24 sec.). [unnumbered, numbered by repository]
    - Kisses sweeter than wine, 1997 (Cassette V6)
      1 videocassette (VHS). [unnumbered, numbered by repository]
    - Open score, 1997 (Cassette V7)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (34 min.). [unnumbered, numbered by repository]
  - Island Eye Island Ear - Knavelskär Island, 1974 (Box 234, Reel F3-F8)
    6 film reels of 6 (super 8). [unnumbered, numbered by repository] Reformatted use copies available.
    Film titles and descriptions have been transcribed from the housing of the original reels.
    - "K - Coast/boat;" "coastline" (Reel F3)
    - "K-1 throws 1 & 2;" "Gulls departure 1-2" (Reel F4)
    - "K 2-8 throws" (Reel F5)
    - "K-Throws 9-18" (Reel F6)
    - "K throws 19-25" (Reel F7)
    - "Knavelskär May 73" (Reel F8)
  - Island Eye Island Ear, 1978 (Box 235, Reel F9-F38)
    30 film reels of 30 (super 8).[unnumbered, numbered by repository] Reformatted use copies available.
    - "Kluver #1" (Reel F9)
    - "Kluver #2" (Reel F10)
    - "Kluver #3" (Reel F11)
    - "Kluver #4" (Reel F12)
    - "Kluver #5" (Reel F13)
    - "Fujiko + Boat" (Reel F14)
    - "Kluver #7" (Reel F15)
    - "Kluver #8" (Reel F16)
    - "Kluver #9" (Reel F17)
    - "Kluver #10" (Reel F18)
    - "Bluff Island - film of photography of sites, first roll OKAY" (Reel F19)
    - "Bluff Island - film of photography of sites, first roll WORK" (Reel F20)
    - "First of 4 Boat films of Bluff Island coast Sept 25 OKAY" (Reel F21)
    - "Bluff Coast from boat from Bluff to South Tip September 27 WORK" (Reel F22)
    - "Bluff coastline from boat from North Cove to Bluff WORK" (Reel F23)
    - "Bluff Island - running around island from tail to bluff OKAY, but slow, exposure good" (Reel F24)
    - "Bluff Island - Running across island from 2nd (eastern) dock/picnic area, toward head through amphitheatre, 3rd + 2nd pine areas OKAY, BUT SLOW" (Reel F25)
    - "Running from Bluff on Bluff Island, to head, around head, back to pine needle slope on body OKAY SLOW" (Reel F26)
    - "BOAT Bluff Island - Western tip to Eastern Head- North side - WORK, BUT BETTER" (Reel F27)
    - "First of two rolls of Airshow Sept 24 OKAY" (Reel F28)
    - "Snow take-off + red plane climbing and diving Sept 24" (Reel F29)
    - "1st trip from water" (Reel F30-31)
    - "1st trip on land" (Reel F32)
    - "Bluff" (Reel F33)
    - "2nd trip" (Reel F34)
    - "2nd trip water bluff" (Reel F35)
    - Unlabled (Reel F36-38)
  - Island Eye Island Ear - Bluff Island, 1978 (Box 236, Reel F39-F66)
    28 film reels of 28 (super 8).[unnumbered, numbered by repository] Reformatted use copies available.
    - "Boat movie with sign 'Bluff Island'" (Reel F39)
    - "Boat movie - N side from Billy's tree to tip, around tip and back again w/ shots of whole N. side" (Reel F40)
    - "North side, showing two decks, Billy's tree and beginning of open tip" (Reel F41)
    - "Bluff on-land, Roll 1- West tip" (Reel F42)
    - "Bluff boat movie - South Coast from West tip to 3rd bluff" (Reel F43)
    - "Bluff on-land, 2nd pine knoll, 2nd picnic, rock face in 2nd picnic, stair to Western bluff, begin top of bluff" (Reel F44)
    - "Bluff on-land - BB slope antenna 5 spot 2nd Bluff (Jog) Gully" (Reel F45)
    - "Bluff/on-land - 1st pine knoll, walk to picnic area (1st) + Pan walk to 2nd Pine Knoll (approach)" (Reel F46)
    - "Bluff/on-land - from flat rock over jagged face - walk to Big Bluff pans inland and along rock to water and south coast to East" (Reel F47)
    - "Bluff/on-land - Tail coast from W bluff - rock on W bluff - features: (backtrack) - spot found w/ David - small face in wood - flat stone over jagged face" (Reel F48)
    - "Bluff/boat movie - Big Bluff, around head to N cove" (Reel F49)
    - "Bluff/on-land - Top of West Bluff - look into BB slop - small knoll - walking shots to top of BB slope" (Reel F50)
    - "Bluff/on-land - end of walk in cedar between 1st + 2nd pine slope - shots of 2nd pine - rocks and rock wall in 3rd + other shots" (Reel F51)
    - "Bluff/on-land - 4th pine area (amphitheater) - 6 boulders at top - pan from ledge - inside slope of ledge/face - walk to 2nd picnic - rock face in 2nd picnic" (Reel F52)
    - "Bluff/on land - last reel - 4th pine slope to 2nd picnic - BOAT fast panning N shore dock to dock to tip S shore cove" (Reel F53)
    - "Bluff - Head: pan of picnic area - tree growing on stone - 2 shots of S cove - begin walk north on East of head" (Reel F54)
    - Continued I.E.I.E footage, no description provided (Reel F55-F58)
    - "Bluff Island - 1st pine slope inc. line of boulders - cedar grove walk begins" (Reel F59)
    - "Bluff on-land - 4th bluff (kites) - into woods - across S cove - walk to N cove and bridge to head - rocks in N cove" (Reel F60)
    - "Bluff on-land - Below 3rd bluff - Pine arrow w/ cedar 1800 ring - begin 4th bluff" (Reel F61)
    - "Boat movie - Bluff boat - North cove - Aerial" (Reel F62)
    - "Boat movie - Bluff Island south side from W tip to BB slope" (Reel F63)
    - "1st aerial of Bluff - First roll of 2 on Sept. 27, 1978 OKAY" (Reel F64)
    - "Aerial Bluff Is. - Shots on Bluff Is. + coast from boat GOOD" (Reel F65)
    - "Aerial Bluff Island GOOD" (Reel F66)
- Posters, 1966-1996; Series IX.; 39 items 1 roll and 4 flat file folders
  Contains posters and graphics published by E.A.T. and others for its projects. Includes posters designed by Rauschenberg, Christo, James Rosenquist, Tom Gormley, Manfred Schroeder and Ken Knowlton.
  - Computer-generated "Nude" by Ken Knowlton and Leon Harmon, Bell Laboratories, undated (Oversize 1**)
    2 four ft. long and 2 six ft. long in black and day-glo green. The reclining nude represented the first experiment to scan a photograph into a computer and reconstitute it with a gray scale, using 12 discreet levels of gray, produced by mathematical and electronic symbols. The scanning process established a certain level of gray in a certain area of the photograph and replaced it with one of the symbols. This process was used to try to establish the minimum amount of information the human eye needed to resolve an image. The image of Deborah Hay in the nude was photographed by Max Mathews. The original computer output was a photograph and was given to E.E. David, who, when he became President Nixon's science adviser, gave it to the Philadelphia Museum of Art.
  - Highway Poster Project, 1972 (Oversize 9**)
    co-sponsored by the Foundation for Automation and Employment and printed at the Lithographic Center, Local One, Amalgamated Lithographers of America. Lithograph, edition size of 150. The following artists made posters about the problems created by putting more emphasis on highways rather than mass transit systems:
  - Computer-generated images by Manfred Schroeder, Bell Labs, silk-screens, 1968 (Oversize 10**)
    Image of an eye configured as a target, 1 in black and 1 in day-glo green; a girl's head, made with the words, "A picture is worth a thousand words," 1 in black and 1 in day-glo green; and of the Brooklyn Museum (Some More Beginnings) show, using the same computer processing as the reclining nude, 1 in black and 1 in day-glo green. 6 items
  - 8 Posters (Oversize 11**)
    - 9 Evenings, 1966
      designed by Rauschenberg, signed by all participants, edition size of 50, numbered H.C. 4 of 14.
    - Quarry Poster, 1968
      by Rauschenberg, printed at the Lithographic Center, Local One, Amalgamated Lithographers of America, as the first project of The Quarry, a collaboration between E.A.T. and Local One, ALA, under which artists would work with master lithographers at the ALA Lithographic Center. Signed, unnumbered.
    - Some More Beginnings, 1969
      designed by Tom Gormley for the subway, edition size of 50. Signed, no. 1.
    - E.A.T. USC, 1970
      Experiments in Art and Technology in Process, published by E.A.T. LA for three days of events and exhibitions at USC, May 1-3, 1970, 2 different posters, unsigned (one printed FOY '70) and unnumbered.
    - Pepsi Pavilion, 1970
      printed in Japan, Shunk-Kender photograph of interior of the mirror dome. It shows a rehearsal of the work by Remy Charlip, "Homage to Loie Fuller," performed at the opening ceremonies. The photograph is printed upside down to emphasize the three-dimensionality of the real image the concave mirror dome produced. Signed by all artist/engineer participants, unnumbered.
    - Projects Outside Art, 1970
      announcement and request for submissions for a planned exhibition. The image represents a rain forest.
    - American Artists in India, 1970
      silk-screen designed and printed by Tom Gormley, using a photograph by Shunk-Kender of a hand position in traditional Indian dance by Chandraleka. Signed by Gormley, Shunk-Kender and Chandraleka, no. 12 of 100.
  - 3 Posters, 1971-1996 (Oversize 12**)
    - 1871-1981 Utopier & Visioner, Moderna Museet, Stockholm; and Erró poster, 1971
      poster announcing all the projects involved in the exhibition, including "Telex: Q&A" with another poster by Erró with faces of communards surrounded by faces of cultural figures from the 19th and 20th centuries. Signature is stamped.
    - Utopia & Visions, Telex Q&A, 1971
      published by E.A.T. Japan, under the direction of Nakaya, with photographs of people who visited the telex center.
    - Art Cash Benefit, 1971
      poster announcing the fund-raising gambling night event at Automation House; and 3 Art Cash flats, one for each side of the bills and one printed on both sides, signed in pencil by the artists, except Warhol who stamped his.
    - New York Collection for Stockholm, 1973
      poster by Rauschenberg, published by Moderna Museet, unsigned; and menu by Red Grooms for SAS flight New York-Stockholm for opening Oct 1973.
    - Artists for New York Benefit, 1979